import { QuizQuestion } from "@/types/quiz-data";

export const languagesToLearn = [
  { label: "Spanish", value: "es" },
  { label: "English", value: "eg" },
  // { label: "French", value: "fr" },
  // { label: "German", value: "de" },
  // { label: "Italian", value: "it" },
  // { label: "Japanese", value: "ja" },
  // { label: "Korean", value: "ko" },
  // { label: "Mandarin Chinese", value: "zh" },
] as const;

export const proficiencyLevels = [
  { label: "Beginner", value: "1" },
  { label: "Intermediate", value: "2" },
  { label: "Advanced", value: "3" },
] as const;

export const contentCategories = [
  { label: "Travel", value: "travel" },
  { label: "Food", value: "food" },
  { label: "Sports", value: "sports" },
  { label: "Music", value: "music" },
  { label: "News", value: "news" },
  { label: "Career", value: "career" },
  { label: "Education", value: "education" },
  { label: "Lifestyle", value: "lifestyle" },
  { label: "Fashion", value: "fashion" },
] as const;

export const MOCK_VIDEOS = [
  {
    id: "1",
    url: "https://storage.googleapis.com/gtv-videos-bucket/sample/ForBiggerBlazes.mp4",
    caption: "Amazing views! #views",
    likes: 1234,
    username: "@viewer",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    url: "https://storage.googleapis.com/gtv-videos-bucket/sample/ForBiggerEscapes.mp4",
    caption: "Dance moves ðŸ•º #dance",
    likes: 5678,
    username: "@dancer",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    url: "https://storage.googleapis.com/gtv-videos-bucket/sample/ForBiggerFun.mp4",
    caption: "Fun times! ðŸŽ‰ #fun",
    likes: 9012,
    username: "@funtime",
  },
];

export const quizData: QuizQuestion[][] = [
  [
    {
      question: "Where was the speaker sleeping recently?",
      answers: ["In a hotel", "Under a bridge", "At home", "On the beach"],
      correct_answer: "Under a bridge",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the speaker drinking now?",
      answers: ["Water", "Juice", "Champagne", "Soda"],
      correct_answer: "Champagne",
    },
    {
      question: "Where is the speaker currently located?",
      answers: [
        "Under a bridge",
        "In a small boat",
        "On the world's largest ship",
        "At a party",
      ],
      correct_answer: "On the world's largest ship",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where was the speaker sleeping recently?",
      answers: ["In a hotel", "Under a bridge", "At home", "On the beach"],
      correct_answer: "Under a bridge",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the speaker drinking now?",
      answers: ["Water", "Juice", "Champagne", "Soda"],
      correct_answer: "Champagne",
    },
    {
      question: "Where is the speaker currently located?",
      answers: [
        "Under a bridge",
        "In a small boat",
        "On the world's largest ship",
        "At a party",
      ],
      correct_answer: "On the world's largest ship",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where was the speaker sleeping recently?",
      answers: ["In a hotel", "Under a bridge", "At home", "On the beach"],
      correct_answer: "Under a bridge",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the speaker drinking now?",
      answers: ["Water", "Juice", "Champagne", "Soda"],
      correct_answer: "Champagne",
    },
    {
      question: "Where is the speaker currently located?",
      answers: [
        "Under a bridge",
        "In a small boat",
        "On the world's largest ship",
        "At a party",
      ],
      correct_answer: "On the world's largest ship",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where was the speaker sleeping recently?",
      answers: ["In a hotel", "Under a bridge", "At home", "On the beach"],
      correct_answer: "Under a bridge",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the speaker drinking now?",
      answers: ["Water", "Juice", "Champagne", "Soda"],
      correct_answer: "Champagne",
    },
    {
      question: "Where is the speaker currently located?",
      answers: [
        "Under a bridge",
        "In a small boat",
        "On the world's largest ship",
        "At a party",
      ],
      correct_answer: "On the world's largest ship",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What Barcelona park does the speaker love?",
      answers: [
        "Ciutadella Park",
        "Parque GÃ¼ell",
        "MontjuÃ¯c Park",
        "Labyrinth Park",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Parque GÃ¼ell",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Parque GÃ¼ell known for having?",
      answers: ["Beaches", "Colorful sculptures", "Zoos", "Amusement rides"],
      correct_answer: "Colorful sculptures",
    },
    {
      question: "What activity does the speaker enjoy at the park?",
      answers: [
        "Swimming",
        "Walking the trails",
        "Playing sports",
        "Having picnics",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Walking the trails",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where was the speaker sleeping recently?",
      answers: ["In a hotel", "Under a bridge", "At home", "On the beach"],
      correct_answer: "Under a bridge",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the speaker drinking now?",
      answers: ["Water", "Juice", "Champagne", "Soda"],
      correct_answer: "Champagne",
    },
    {
      question: "Where is the speaker currently located?",
      answers: [
        "Under a bridge",
        "In a small boat",
        "On the world's largest ship",
        "At a party",
      ],
      correct_answer: "On the world's largest ship",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where was the speaker sleeping recently?",
      answers: ["In a hotel", "Under a bridge", "At home", "On the beach"],
      correct_answer: "Under a bridge",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the speaker drinking now?",
      answers: ["Water", "Juice", "Champagne", "Soda"],
      correct_answer: "Champagne",
    },
    {
      question: "Where is the speaker currently located?",
      answers: [
        "Under a bridge",
        "In a small boat",
        "On the world's largest ship",
        "At a party",
      ],
      correct_answer: "On the world's largest ship",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What should you see in Costa Rica?",
      answers: ["Big cities", "The rainforest", "Snowy mountains", "Deserts"],
      correct_answer: "The rainforest",
    },
    {
      question: "Which animals can you find in Costa Rica's rainforest?",
      answers: [
        "Penguins and seals",
        "Monkeys and toucans",
        "Lions and tigers",
        "Polar bears and walruses",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Monkeys and toucans",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the Pacific coast beaches good for?",
      answers: [
        "Skiing",
        "Surfing and relaxing",
        "Ice skating",
        "Mountain climbing",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Surfing and relaxing",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What should you see in Costa Rica?",
      answers: ["Big cities", "The rainforest", "Snowy mountains", "Deserts"],
      correct_answer: "The rainforest",
    },
    {
      question: "Which animals can you find in Costa Rica's rainforest?",
      answers: [
        "Penguins and seals",
        "Monkeys and toucans",
        "Lions and tigers",
        "Polar bears and walruses",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Monkeys and toucans",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the Pacific coast beaches good for?",
      answers: [
        "Skiing",
        "Surfing and relaxing",
        "Ice skating",
        "Mountain climbing",
      ],
      correct_answer: "Surfing and relaxing",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where was the speaker sleeping recently?",
      answers: ["In a hotel", "Under a bridge", "At home", "On the beach"],
      correct_answer: "Under a bridge",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the speaker drinking now?",
      answers: ["Water", "Juice", "Champagne", "Soda"],
      correct_answer: "Champagne",
    },
    {
      question: "Where is the speaker currently located?",
      answers: [
        "Under a bridge",
        "In a small boat",
        "On the world's largest ship",
        "At a party",
      ],
      correct_answer: "On the world's largest ship",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where was the speaker sleeping recently?",
      answers: ["In a hotel", "Under a bridge", "At home", "On the beach"],
      correct_answer: "Under a bridge",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the speaker drinking now?",
      answers: ["Water", "Juice", "Champagne", "Soda"],
      correct_answer: "Champagne",
    },
    {
      question: "Where is the speaker currently located?",
      answers: [
        "Under a bridge",
        "In a small boat",
        "On the world's largest ship",
        "At a party",
      ],
      correct_answer: "On the world's largest ship",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where is this plan located near?",
      answers: ["Valencia", "Caracas", "Maracaibo", "MÃ©rida"],
      correct_answer: "Caracas",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Arte Murano in Potrerito?",
      answers: ["A museum", "A glass factory", "A restaurant", "A park"],
      correct_answer: "A glass factory",
    },
    {
      question: "What raw material is transformed into glass?",
      answers: ["Clay", "Metal", "Sand", "Plastic"],
      correct_answer: "Sand",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where is this plan located near?",
      answers: ["Valencia", "Caracas", "Maracaibo", "MÃ©rida"],
      correct_answer: "Caracas",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Arte Murano in Potrerito?",
      answers: ["A museum", "A glass factory", "A restaurant", "A park"],
      correct_answer: "A glass factory",
    },
    {
      question: "What raw material is transformed into glass?",
      answers: ["Clay", "Metal", "Sand", "Plastic"],
      correct_answer: "Sand",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where is this plan located near?",
      answers: ["Valencia", "Caracas", "Maracaibo", "MÃ©rida"],
      correct_answer: "Caracas",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Arte Murano in Potrerito?",
      answers: ["A museum", "A glass factory", "A restaurant", "A park"],
      correct_answer: "A glass factory",
    },
    {
      question: "What raw material is transformed into glass?",
      answers: ["Clay", "Metal", "Sand", "Plastic"],
      correct_answer: "Sand",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where is this plan located near?",
      answers: ["Valencia", "Caracas", "Maracaibo", "MÃ©rida"],
      correct_answer: "Caracas",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Arte Murano in Potrerito?",
      answers: ["A museum", "A glass factory", "A restaurant", "A park"],
      correct_answer: "A glass factory",
    },
    {
      question: "What raw material is transformed into glass?",
      answers: ["Clay", "Metal", "Sand", "Plastic"],
      correct_answer: "Sand",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where is this plan located near?",
      answers: ["Valencia", "Caracas", "Maracaibo", "MÃ©rida"],
      correct_answer: "Caracas",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Arte Murano in Potrerito?",
      answers: ["A museum", "A glass factory", "A restaurant", "A park"],
      correct_answer: "A glass factory",
    },
    {
      question: "What raw material is transformed into glass?",
      answers: ["Clay", "Metal", "Sand", "Plastic"],
      correct_answer: "Sand",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where is this plan located near?",
      answers: ["Valencia", "Caracas", "Maracaibo", "MÃ©rida"],
      correct_answer: "Caracas",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Arte Murano in Potrerito?",
      answers: ["A museum", "A glass factory", "A restaurant", "A park"],
      correct_answer: "A glass factory",
    },
    {
      question: "What raw material is transformed into glass?",
      answers: ["Clay", "Metal", "Sand", "Plastic"],
      correct_answer: "Sand",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "Where is this plan located near?",
      answers: ["Valencia", "Caracas", "Maracaibo", "MÃ©rida"],
      correct_answer: "Caracas",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Arte Murano in Potrerito?",
      answers: ["A museum", "A glass factory", "A restaurant", "A park"],
      correct_answer: "A glass factory",
    },
    {
      question: "What raw material is transformed into glass?",
      answers: ["Clay", "Metal", "Sand", "Plastic"],
      correct_answer: "Sand",
    },
  ],
];

export const CDNURL =
  "https://lhayczdxenefkmxgdgif.supabase.co/storage/v1/object/public/videos/";
